<events>
<event category="Microsoft">
<title lang="en">Microsoft Events Catalog</title>
<url>https://events.microsoft.com</url>
<dateStart>Jan-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>Dec-2022</dateEnd>
<description>A fully-searchable catalog of events conducted by Microsoft and their partners.</description>
</event>
<event category="Microsoft">
<title lang="en">Microsoft Ignite</title>
<url>https://myignite.microsoft.com/home</url>
<dateStart>TBD 2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>TBD 2022</dateEnd>
<description>Until our next event experience, check out the latest learning opportunities, recent event highlights, and more.</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">BI LATAM Summit 2022</title>
<url>https://www.bilatam.org/bilatamsummit2022</url>
<dateStart>19-Feb-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>19-Feb-2022</dateEnd>
<description>BI LATAM Summit es la evento online más grande del año de profesionales de Ciencia de Datos, Inteligencia de Negocios y Plataformas de Datos en español. Comparte con nosotros en este evento en línea y gratuito.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
 <title lang="en">SQLBits</title>
<url>www.sqlbits.com</url>
<dateStart>08-March-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>12-March-2022</dateEnd>
<description>SQLBits is back in London for 2022 on the 8 - 12 March at ExCel, with the new five day format, for a marathon of top quality training from global specialists. At a time of change if you want to learn about the new paradigms in data platforms, SQLBits is the place.
Join us in-person or virtually, the choice is yours. We have two days of full-day training sessions and three days of general sessions, and as always the Saturday is free to attend.
Registration and more information coming soon. Sign up to be notified of updates</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">Citus Con: An Event for Postgres</title>
<url>https://www.citusdata.com/cituscon/2022/</url>
<dateStart>12-April-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>12-April-2022</dateEnd>
<description>Citus Con: An Event for Postgres is a free and virtual developer event happening April 12-13, 2022 — organized by the Postgres team at Microsoft. 
There will be livestream talks in 3 geographies, plus on-demand talks too—from Citus open- source users, Azure Database for PostgreSQL customers, and experts in Postgres and Citus. 
Schedule is now live! </description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">SQL Server and AzureSQL Conference - Las Vegas </title>
<url>https://www.devintersection.com/#!/?track=sql</url>
<dateStart>05-Apr-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>07-Apr-2022</dateEnd>
<description>THE INTERSECTION OF CO-LOCATED TECHNOLOGY EVENTS: Microsoft SQL Server Azure SQL Conference and Azure + AI Conference
Azure Data and SQL Community are coming together in Las Vegas, April 2022. Join Microsoft Executives and members of the Azure Data product group for sessions and keynotes where they share new releases and where the future will take the tech industry.

This is the largest in-person event in two years featuring 200+ in depth sessions delivered by your favorite Microsoft engineers and industry experts in addition to 20+ full day workshops.
</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">Azure Cosmos DB Conf</title>
<url>https://gotcosmos.com/conf</url>
<dateStart>19-April-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>19-April-2022</dateEnd>
<description>Azure Cosmos DB Conf returns on April 19 - 20, 2022. It is a free virtual developer event organized in collaboration with the Azure Cosmos DB community, with sessions delivered by community members and the Microsoft team.  The event will be streamed in segments across multiple timezones.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">Data Saturday Stockholm 2022</title>
<url>https://datasatsto.se/</url>
<dateStart>21-May-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>21-May-2022</dateEnd>
<description>Attend this free, one-day conference in Stockholm to sharpen your skills on the Microsoft data platform, and to connect to other professionals in your space! We’ll offer sessions from leading world-class international and local speakers, across data management, cloud and hybrid architecture, analytics and BI, and so much more.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">DataGrillen 2022</title>
<url>http://www.DataGrillen.com</url>
<dateStart>02-June-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>03-June-2022</dateEnd>
<description>Databases, Bratwurst, Bier
The most flavoursome Data Platform event on the planet</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">PowerShell Conference Europe</title>
<url>https://psconf.eu</url>
<dateStart>20-June-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>20-June-2022</dateEnd>
<description>Discover what professionals around the globe are doing to solve real-world problems!
Beyond PowerShell, today's engineers need to understand DevOps and increasingly evolve in the cloud. Meet the welcoming PowerShell community and talk as equals. At the PowerShell Conference Europe you can sit and talk with anyone - speakers, attendees, members of the product team. Share your code and show how you are solving problems so that others can learn from you. You can also learn from those that have a different approach to the same problem. Often, people team up after events to join forces to tackle common problems to build fantastic solutions.</description>
</event>
</events>
