<events>
<event category="Microsoft">
<title lang="en">Microsoft Events Catalog</title>
<url>https://events.microsoft.com</url>
<dateStart>Jan-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>Dec-2023</dateEnd>
<description>A fully-searchable catalog of events conducted by Microsoft and their partners.</description>
</event>
<event category="Microsoft">
<title lang="en">Microsoft Ignite</title>
<url>https://myignite.microsoft.com/home</url>
<dateStart>Nov 15, 2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>Nov 16, 2023</dateEnd>
<description>Until our next event experience, check out the latest learning opportunities, recent event highlights, and more.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Azure Data Conference - Orlando </title>
<url>https://azuredataconf.com/</url>
<dateStart>Dec 3, 2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>Dec 8, 2023</dateEnd>
<description>
Join your favorite Microsoft leaders and engineers as they share their excitement about the future of Microsoft technologies. Their keynotes set the stage for this great learning event. 

The Microsoft engineers presenting will take a deep dive with you into the many new technology releases, including the latest updates to SQL Server, Azure SQL, and the entire Azure Data Platform.

You’ll also have the opportunity to spend time with Microsoft engineers and industry experts you know and trust to present real-world solutions and tips for productivity. Join other leaders from the Azure Data Community to connect, network and grow!
</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">Azure Data Explorer in a Day - Americas</title>
<url>https://aka.ms/adxinadayamericas</url>
<dateStart>22-Mar-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>22-Mar-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Azure Data Explorer (ADX) in a Day is an 8-hour workshop, to get familiar with Exabyte scale analytics service using ADX, Kusto Query Language, Timeseries Analytics and Dashboards through a hands-on learning experience from data ingestion to visualization. Please find more details at https://aka.ms/adxinaday

Agenda:

60 mins - Presentation
150 mins - Lab 1 hands-on
60 mins - Lunch/Dinner break
45 mins - Presentation
150 mins - Lab 2 hands-on
15 mins - Wrap up/Closing</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Saturday Costa Rica 2023 (#1044)</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2023-04-01-sqlsaturday1044/</url>
<dateStart>01-Apr-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>01-Apr-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Free one day conference for database professionals.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
 <title lang="en">Citus Con: An Event for Postgres</title>
<url>https://www.citusdata.com/cituscon/2023 </url>
<dateStart>18-Apr-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>19-Apr-2023</dateEnd>
<description> Citus Con is a free and virtual developer event happening April 18-19, 2023—organized by the Citus and Postgres team at Microsoft.  Join us to hear from open source users, Azure database customers, and experts in PostgreSQL and Citus about how they use Postgres. 
 
There will be 2 unique livestreams happening at different times of day, plus on-demand talks too—from Citus open- source users, Azure Cosmos DB for Postgres and Azure Database for PostgreSQL customers, and experts in Postgres and Citus.  

Talks are 25 minutes long and in English.  Check out the #CitusCon Call for Speakers. (Hurry, the CFP closes February 6. ) 

</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Saturday Haiti 2023 (#1050)</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2023-04-29-sqlsaturday1050/</url>
<dateStart>29-Apr-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>29-Apr-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Virtual one day conference for data professionals in French</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Saturday Jacksonville 2023 (#1041)</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2023-05-06-sqlsaturday1041/</url>
<dateStart>06-May-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>06-May-2023</dateEnd>
<description>SQL Saturday is a training event for SQL Server and data professionals who want to learn how to elevate their careers to the next level. This is the 15th year of SQL Saturday in Jacksonville and will be held on May 6, 2023. 
 Admittance to this event is free, all costs are covered by donations and sponsorship. Please register soon as seating is limited 
 Friday, SQL Sat Jax runs 2 pre-con tracks and this year they welcome Bob Ward (SQL Server 2022) and Ginger Grant (Azure Synapse and PowerBI).</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Saturday New York City 2023 (#1048)</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2023-05-06-sqlsaturday1048/</url>
<dateStart>06-May-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>06-May-2023</dateEnd>
<description>SQL Saturday New York City is a one day, free training event for data platform professionals, hosted at the Microsoft Technology Center in Times Square.</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en"">SQL Saturday Salt Lake City</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/slc/</url>
<dateStart>13-May-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>13-May-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Free one day conference for data professionals. SQL Saturday Salt Lake City will be an in person event this year and will have 4 tracks.</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Saturday South Florida 2023 (#1053)</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2023-06-03-sqlsaturday1053/</url>
<dateStart>03-Jun-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>03-Jun-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Free one day conference for data professionals</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">PSConfEU</title>
<url>https://psconf.eu/</url>
<dateStart>19-Jun-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>22-Jun-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Join us June 19th-22nd 2023 at Cubex Centrum, Prague, Czech Republic to discover what professionals around the globe are doing to solve real-world problems! 
 Beyond PowerShell, today's engineers need to understand DevOps and increasingly evolve in the cloud. Meet the welcoming PowerShell community and talk as equals. At the PowerShell Conference Europe you can sit and talk with anyone - speakers, attendees, members of the product team. 
 Share your code and show how you are solving problems so that others can learn from you and learn from those that have a different approach to the same problem. </description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Saturday Ica 2023 (#1051)</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2023-06-24-sqlsaturday1051/</url>
<dateStart>24-Jun-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>24-Jun-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Free one day conference for data professionals</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQLKonferenz</title>
<url>https://sqlkonferenz.de/</url>
<dateStart>11-Sept-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>11-Sept-2023</dateEnd>
<description>SQLKonferenz is the largest conference for the Microsoft Data Platform in the DACH region. It is a conference organized by the German Microsoft Data Platform Community (PASS Deutschland e.V.). The conference is established since 2014 and holds german and english speaking tracks. The conference venue is located this year in HANA, which is 40km from Frankfurt International Airport in the middle of Germany. </description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Saturday Denver 2023 (#1056)</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2023-09-23-sqlsaturday1056/</url>
<dateStart>23-Sept-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>23-Sept-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Free one day conference for data professionals</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Saturday Boston 2023</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2023-10-14-sqlsaturday1046/</url>
<dateStart>14-Oct-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>14-Oct-2023</dateEnd>
<description>SQL Saturday is a one-day free training event for people that work with the Microsoft Data Platform
SQL Saturday Boston 2023 will take place on October 14th, 2023, at the Microsoft Burlington office.
This is a free event for the tech community organized by SQLSatuday and New England SQL Server User Group (NESQL) We encourage you to register early.

Precon on October 13th, 2023: Mastering Query Tuning by Brent Ozar</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">PostgreSQL Conference Europe</title>
<url>https://2023.pgconf.eu/</url>
<dateStart>12-Dec-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>15-Dec-2023</dateEnd>
<description>PostgreSQL Conference Europe is by far the largest PostgreSQL conference in Europe.

Over a decade of PostgreSQL
The conference is organised by PostgreSQL Europe, with participation from most of the PostgreSQL user groups around Europe, and is intended to be an important meeting and cooperation point for users both in and out of Europe.

PGConf.EU is a unique chance for European PostgreSQL users and developers to catch up, learn, build relationships, get to know each other and consolidate a real network of professionals that use and work with PostgreSQL.
</description>
</event>
</events>
