<events>
<event category="Microsoft">
<title lang="en">Microsoft Events Catalog</title>
<url>https://events.microsoft.com</url>
<dateStart>Jan-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>Dec-2023</dateEnd>
<description>A fully-searchable catalog of events conducted by Microsoft and their partners.</description>
</event>
<event category="Microsoft">
<title lang="en">Microsoft Ignite</title>
<url>https://myignite.microsoft.com/home</url>
<dateStart>Nov 15, 2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>Nov 16, 2023</dateEnd>
<description>Until our next event experience, check out the latest learning opportunities, recent event highlights, and more.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Azure Data Conference - Orlando </title>
<url>https://azuredataconf.com/</url>
<dateStart>Dec 3, 2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>Dec 8, 2023</dateEnd>
<description>
Join your favorite Microsoft leaders and engineers as they share their excitement about the future of Microsoft technologies. Their keynotes set the stage for this great learning event. 

The Microsoft engineers presenting will take a deep dive with you into the many new technology releases, including the latest updates to SQL Server, Azure SQL, and the entire Azure Data Platform.

You’ll also have the opportunity to spend time with Microsoft engineers and industry experts you know and trust to present real-world solutions and tips for productivity. Join other leaders from the Azure Data Community to connect, network and grow!
</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">PSConfEU</title>
<url>https://psconf.eu/</url>
<dateStart>19-Jun-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>22-Jun-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Join us June 19th-22nd 2023 at Cubex Centrum, Prague, Czech Republic to discover what professionals around the globe are doing to solve real-world problems! 
 Beyond PowerShell, today's engineers need to understand DevOps and increasingly evolve in the cloud. Meet the welcoming PowerShell community and talk as equals. At the PowerShell Conference Europe you can sit and talk with anyone - speakers, attendees, members of the product team. 
 Share your code and show how you are solving problems so that others can learn from you and learn from those that have a different approach to the same problem. </description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">Data Toboggan</title>
<url>https://www.meetup.com/data-toboggan/events/293548150/</url>
<dateStart>24-Jun-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>24-Jun-2023</dateEnd>
<description>We're back, and this time we're bigger (and hopefully better) than ever.. again !!

2 tracks covering all your favourite Azure Synapse Analytics content, from world-class speakers, some new voices, and perhaps one or two surprises (Fabric maybe?!)

We're keeping the shorter-format talks as well, so whatever you're interested in, there's sure to be *loads* of content for you to enjoy!</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Saturday Ica 2023 (#1051)</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2023-06-24-sqlsaturday1051/</url>
<dateStart>24-Jun-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>24-Jun-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Free one day conference for data professionals</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">Data Saturday Johannesburg</title>
<url>https://datasaturdays.com/2023-08-05-datasaturday0036/</url>
<dateStart>05-Aug-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>05-Aug-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Data Saturday Johannesburg is a free, full-day, volunteer-led, in-person event that covers a variety of topics within the Microsoft data platform ecosystem. The event will take place in the Microsoft offices in Johannesburg, South Africa.

Previously known as SQL Saturday Johannesburg, this event provides attendees with the opportunity to interact with their fellow data professionals to network and discuss challenges and solutions to some of their most pressing challenges.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">DataSaturday Oslo</title>
<url>oslo.datasaturday.no</url>
<dateStart>02-Sept-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>02-Sept-2023</dateEnd>
<description>DataSaturday Oslo is back again! This year we have 3 pre-cons on September 1st as well as 36 hour long sessions on the main event September 2nd. You can gain in-depth knowledge about the brand new Microsoft Fabric in both pre-con as well as regular sessions! As allways, the main event is free except for if you want lunch included.</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQLKonferenz</title>
<url>https://sqlkonferenz.de/</url>
<dateStart>11-Sept-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>11-Sept-2023</dateEnd>
<description>SQLKonferenz is the largest conference for the Microsoft Data Platform in the DACH region. It is a conference organized by the German Microsoft Data Platform Community (PASS Deutschland e.V.). The conference is established since 2014 and holds german and english speaking tracks. The conference venue is located this year in HANA, which is 40km from Frankfurt International Airport in the middle of Germany. </description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Saturday Denver 2023 (#1056)</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2023-09-23-sqlsaturday1056/</url>
<dateStart>23-Sept-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>23-Sept-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Free one day conference for data professionals</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">Data Moshpit</title>
<url>Http://www.data-moshpit.com</url>
<dateStart>16-Sept-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>16-Sept-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Data Moshpit is the Metal themed Data Saturday taking place in September 2023. In a Metal Club (yes, you read right M e t a l  C l u b) in Berlin! There will be international speakers. There will be Data. There will be beer and good food. There will be a concert in the evening and of course there will be METAL!!!</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">Future Data Driven Summit</title>
<url>https://datadrivencommunity.com/FutureDataDriven2023.html</url>
<dateStart>27-Sept-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>27-Sept-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Future Data Driven Summit is a marquee, online event focusing on the comprehensive Microsoft Data Platform. Our mission is to inform and update attendees with Data and AI, DevOps and DataOps, PowerBI and Visualization, Integration and Automation, and cloud infrastructure. We are excited to welcome you to participate at our free first ever Future Data Driven online event.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Saturday Boston 2023</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2023-10-14-sqlsaturday1046/</url>
<dateStart>14-Oct-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>14-Oct-2023</dateEnd>
<description>SQL Saturday is a one-day free training event for people that work with the Microsoft Data Platform
SQL Saturday Boston 2023 will take place on October 14th, 2023, at the Microsoft Burlington office.
This is a free event for the tech community organized by SQLSatuday and New England SQL Server User Group (NESQL) We encourage you to register early.

Precon on October 13th, 2023: Mastering Query Tuning by Brent Ozar</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">dataMinds Connect</title>
<url>https://datamindsconnect.be/</url>
<dateStart>09-Oct-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>09-Oct-2023</dateEnd>
<description>dataMinds Connect is a 2 day in-person event in the wonderful city of Mechelen, Belgium. It's an IT related event with a specific focus on the Microsoft Data Platform. 

While some people may still refer back to the original name of SQL Server Days, we've adopted our dataMinds Connect brand 6 years ago keeping in mind the same core values. 2 days filled with learning, networking and a whole lot of laughs while doing so! 

This year will be the 16th edition of the conference, and running for the seventh time as dataMinds Connect. Aiming to bring together all people with a passion for the Microsoft Data Platform, in all flavours possible, we're hoping to reunite with our many community members in person again, and share our common passion. Reunite with old and familiar faces, and embrace a lot of new ones!

Go ahead and clearly mark Monday October 9th and Tuesday October 10th 2023 in your schedule, as these will be 2 days you don't want to miss!</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">New Stars of Data 2023 </title>
<url>Https://newstarsofdata.com</url>
<dateStart>27-Oct-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>27-Oct-2023</dateEnd>
<description>New Stars of Data is the event for new speakers in the Microsoft Data Platform space.

This online event is the perfect start for people who have not spoken at any large events before. Based on the idea behind the famous ""Newcomer Track"" at DataGrillen; we are searching for the next generation of speakers who want to take their first steps into the realm of presenting their ideas to an audience. 

We offer a mentoring program to each chosen speaker. A mentor is a seasoned speaker who will help craft and practice your session. They will also be on hand during the presentation as a host/mentor and be able to offer the support you need to deliver a fantastic presentation. </description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">Data Bash Live</title>
<url>https://databash.live/</url>
<dateStart>25-Nov-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>25-Nov-2023</dateEnd>
<description>This conference is a free and live, online event (live on YouTube) targeted towards the German-speaking data communities within Europe – mainly Austria, Germany, Fürstentum Lichtenstein and Switzerland. As a result, we’re focusing on speakers from this area, but of course, anyone worldwide may apply as well. We will have session blocks in which speakers are presenting in German, but most sessions will be delivered in English.
 </description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">Live! 360 </title>
<url>https://live360events.com/Events/Orlando-2023/Home.aspx</url>
<dateStart>12-Nov-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>17-Nov-2023</dateEnd>
<description>Live! 360 returns to Orlando, November 12-17, 2023 at the Loews Royal Pacific Resort, Orlando, FL. Live! 360 offers six co-located technical conferences for the Developer, Data, Security, and IT community at one time for one low price. Incorporating knowledge transfer, networking and leading-edge training, these conferences keep attendees up-to-date on current technologies with a look to the future.

Live! 360 is the perfect opportunity to get all the training you need with these co-located conferences:
Visual Studio Live!
SQL Server Live!
TechMentor
Artificial Intelligence Live! 
Cloud and Containers Live!
Cybersecurity and Ransomware Live!</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">PostgreSQL Conference Europe</title>
<url>https://2023.pgconf.eu/</url>
<dateStart>12-Dec-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>15-Dec-2023</dateEnd>
<description>PostgreSQL Conference Europe is by far the largest PostgreSQL conference in Europe.

Over a decade of PostgreSQL
The conference is organised by PostgreSQL Europe, with participation from most of the PostgreSQL user groups around Europe, and is intended to be an important meeting and cooperation point for users both in and out of Europe.

PGConf.EU is a unique chance for European PostgreSQL users and developers to catch up, learn, build relationships, get to know each other and consolidate a real network of professionals that use and work with PostgreSQL.
</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">Data Saturday München </title>
<url>https://datasaturdays.com/2024-02-24-datasaturday0040/</url>
<dateStart>23-Feb-2024</dateStart>
<dateEnd>23-Feb-2024</dateEnd>
<description>Data Saturday München is a free one-day event for professionals who use the Microsoft data platform and Microsoft Azure technologies. This community event offers content across data management, cloud and hybrid architecture, analytics, business intelligence, AI, and much more.

It is being held at the Microsoft Germany Headquarters in Munich.</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">DataGrillen 2024</title>
<url>Https://DataGrillen.com</url>
<dateStart>17-May-2024</dateStart>
<dateEnd>17-May-2024</dateEnd>
<description>DataGrillen is the biggest free Microsoft Data Platform event in Germany.

Our motto is ""Data, Bratwurst and Beer"", which describes our event quite well.

The audience is an international mix and covers all aspects of the Microsoft Data Platform. 
</description>
</event>"
</events>
