<events>
<event category="Microsoft">
<title lang="en">Microsoft Events Catalog</title>
<url>https://events.microsoft.com</url>
<dateStart>Jan-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>Dec-2022</dateEnd>
<description>A fully-searchable catalog of events conducted by Microsoft and their partners.</description>
</event>
<event category="Microsoft">
<title lang="en">Microsoft Ignite</title>
<url>https://myignite.microsoft.com/home</url>
<dateStart>Nov 15, 2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>Nov 16, 2023</dateEnd>
<description>Until our next event experience, check out the latest learning opportunities, recent event highlights, and more.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Azure Data Conference - Orlando </title>
<url>https://azuredataconf.com/#!/</url>
<dateStart>Dec 3, 2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>Dec 8, 2023</dateEnd>
<description>
Join your favorite Microsoft leaders & engineers as they share their excitement about the future of Microsoft technologies. Their keynotes set the stage for this great learning event. 

The Microsoft engineers presenting will take a deep dive with you into the many new technology releases, including the latest updates to SQL Server, Azure SQL, and the entire Azure Data Platform.

You’ll also have the opportunity to spend time with Microsoft engineers and industry experts you know and trust to present real-world solutions and tips for productivity. Join other leaders from the Azure Data Community to connect, network and grow!
</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">PostgreSQL Conference Europe</title>
<url>https://2022.pgconf.eu/</url>
<dateStart>19-Jun-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>22-Jun-2023</dateEnd>
<description>PostgreSQL Conference Europe is by far the largest PostgreSQL conference in Europe.

Over a decade of PostgreSQL
The conference is organised by PostgreSQL Europe, with participation from most of the PostgreSQL user groups around Europe, and is intended to be an important meeting and cooperation point for users both in and out of Europe.

PGConf.EU is a unique chance for European PostgreSQL users and developers to catch up, learn, build relationships, get to know each other and consolidate a real network of professionals that use and work with PostgreSQL.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">Difinity</title>
<url>https://difinity.co.nz/</url>
<dateStart>28-Nov-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>28-Nov-2022</dateEnd>
<description>Microsoft AI, Data, and Power Platform Conference
Difinity is the largest Microsoft Data, AI, Power BI, Power Platform and Business Applications Conference in New Zealand focusing on Data Platform, AI, Business Intelligence, Business Applications, Power Platform, and Analytics. IT Decision Makers, Developers, Business Analysts, IT Professionals, BI Managers, BI Professionals, Database Administrators, Architects, Digital and Big Data business leaders, and Consultants will gather for two consecutive days of learning.

Difinity Conference been running in New Zealand since 2017, and this would be our 5th year’s anniversary event. We want to make it an special event full of learning, fun, and networking opportunities.</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Saturday MN 2022 (#1028)</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2022-12-03-sqlsaturday1028/</url>
<dateStart>03-Dec-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>03-Dec-2022</dateEnd>
<description>SQL Saturday MN 2022 is a free virtaul training event for data platform professionals. #SQLSATMN </description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">SQL Bits 2023</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2023-12-03-sqlsaturday1028/</url>
<dateStart>14-Mar-2023</dateStart>
<dateEnd>18-Mar-2023</dateEnd>
<description> SQLBits is THE conference for leading data professionals to network, develop and share data knowledge. SQLBits is the largest Data Platform conference with over 300 sessions over 5 days covering data technologies, including SQL Server, Azure, Big Data, Power BI, Machine Learning, and more! 
 Born out of the hunger to share the latest developments, solutions and best practice, whilst forming a network of data professionals behind some of the most exciting developments on the Modern Data Platform.
SQLBits provides you with the education, skills and solutions from the people that have created the products, and are leading the field worldwide. This is your chance to meet the people that design and build the products you use and depend on. 
Where?
International Convention Centre, Celtic Manor, Newport, Wales NP18 1HQ 
 </description>
</event>
</events>
