<events>
<event category="Microsoft">
<title lang="en">Microsoft Events Catalog</title>
<url>https://events.microsoft.com</url>
<dateStart>May-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>June-2021</dateEnd>
<description>A fully-searchable catalog of events conducted by Microsoft and their partners.</description>
</event>
<event category="Microsoft">
<title lang="en">Microsoft Ignite</title>
<url>https://myignite.microsoft.com/home</url>
<dateStart>02-Nov-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>04-Nov-2021</dateEnd>
<description>Until our next event experience, check out the latest learning opportunities, recent event highlights, and more.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">New Speaker Library - Call for Sessions</title>
<url>https://sessionize.com/new-stars-speaker-improvement</url>
<dateStart>11-Aug-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>31-Dec-2021</dateEnd>
<description>We're looking for seasoned speakers, willing to share their experience and knowledge to help new and old stars to build better presentations. Potential topics could include but are not limited to:
- creating an abstract
- building a slide deck
- designing session flows
- turning a slide deck into a presentation
- accessible presentations
- inclusive language
- or how to pre-record a session.
Our goal is to build a free content library that’s available to everyone to help them improve their sessions – no matter if it’s their first or 100th, even though we think new speakers will benefit the most.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">SQL Friday Autumn 2021</title>
<url>https://sqlfriday.net</url>
<dateStart>20-Aug-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>17-Dec-2021</dateEnd>
<description>SQL Friday is a weekly online event, happening at noon Central European Time every Friday. One one-hour session is presented in a Microsoft Teams meeting for a live, online audience, then recorded and later published to Youtube. 
The topic for the autumn 2021 season of Sql Friday is Sql Server. SQL Server in containers, Sql Server in the cloud, Sql Server on-premise, T-Sql fundamentals, advanced T-Sql, performance tuning, engine internals, HA/DR overview etc.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">SQL Server and AzureSQL Conference - Las Vegas </title>
<url>https://www.devintersection.com/#!/?track=sql</url>
<dateStart>7-Dec-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>9-Dec-2021</dateEnd>
<description>THE INTERSECTION OF CO-LOCATED TECHNOLOGY EVENTS: Microsoft SQL Server Azure SQL Conference and Azure + AI Conference</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">DataMinutes #2</title>
<url>http://dataminutes.io</url>
<dateStart>21-Jan-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>21-Jan-2022</dateEnd>
<description>DataMinutes is the fastest event in the Microsoft Data Platform space yet!
The whole event will run with 10 minute lightning talks only.
That’s 10 minutes per session with no live Q and A. Q and A will be handled through our website afterwards where we will also be posting recordings of each session.</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Data Toboggan </title>
<url>https://https://www.meetup.com/data-toboggan/events/282340039/</url>
<dateStart>29-Jan-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>29-Jan-2022</dateEnd>
<description>"Join us for our THIRD all-day event specializing in Azure Synapse Analytics !
Azure Synapse Analytics is a practically limitless analytics service that brings together data integration, enterprise data warehousing and big data analytics. Let's spend a day exploring and showcasing these capabilities.
It is this analytical power that will help enable any organisation to transform from being reactive into being truly proactive, generating actionable insights that enable both business flow and timely decision-support."
</description>
</event>
 
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">Data Saturday Stockholm 2022</title>
<url>https://datasatsto.se/</url>
<dateStart>21-May-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>21-May-2022</dateEnd>
<description>Attend this free, one-day conference in Stockholm to sharpen your skills on the Microsoft data platform, and to connect to other professionals in your space! We’ll offer sessions from leading world-class international and local speakers, across data management, cloud and hybrid architecture, analytics and BI, and so much more.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">DataGrillen 2022</title>
<url>http://www.DataGrillen.com</url>
<dateStart>02-June-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>03-June-2022</dateEnd>
<description>Databases, Bratwurst, Bier
The most flavoursome Data Platform event on the planet</description>
</event>
</events>
