<events>
<event category="Microsoft">
<title lang="en">Microsoft Events Catalog</title>
<url>https://events.microsoft.com</url>
<dateStart>May-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>June-2021</dateEnd>
<description>A fully-searchable catalog of events conducted by Microsoft and their partners.</description>
</event>
<event category="Microsoft">
<title lang="en">Microsoft Ignite</title>
<url>https://myignite.microsoft.com/home</url>
<dateStart>Fall TBD</dateStart>
<dateEnd>Fall TBD</dateEnd>
<description>Until our next event experience, check out the latest learning opportunities, recent event highlights, and more.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">Data Geeks Saturday</title>
<url>https://data-geeks.org/data-geeks-saturday/</url>
<dateStart>07-August-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>07-August-2021</dateEnd>
<description>Data Geeks Saturday is a full day of quality training for Data Professionals to learn about Data Platform Development and administration, Business Intelligence, Data and Analytics, Artificial Intelligence, Data Science, IoT Data, Cloud Data, Data Visualization, Personal Branding, Professional Development; to connect with peers, have fun and win prizes!</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Dativerse</title>
<url>https://datagrillen.com/dativerse/</url>
<dateStart>13-Aug-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>13-Aug-2021</dateEnd>
<description>Dativerse is a new event in the Microsoft Data Platform space with the aim that all its speakers contribute to the diversity of the Microsoft Data Platform Community. We try to elevate those that are usually underrepresented at conferences due to their race, gender, sexual orientation, location or any other reason. </description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Beginner Data Science Day</title>
<url>https://wit.sqlugs.com/2021/06/11/data-platform-wit-beginner-data-science-day/</url>
<dateStart>20-August-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>20-August-2021</dateEnd>
<description>We are Data Platform WIT (women-in-tech) group and this is our next day long event featuring women speakers on beginner level data science topics. Our call for speakers is still open. We close CFS 8th August and meetup registration for attendance opens soon after.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">SQL Friday Autumn 2021</title>
<url>https://sqlfriday.net</url>
<dateStart>20-Aug-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>17-Dec-2021</dateEnd>
<description>SQL Friday is a weekly online event, happening at noon Central European Time every Friday. One one-hour session is presented in a Microsoft Teams meeting for a live, online audience, then recorded and later published to Youtube. 
The topic for the autumn 2021 season of Sql Friday is Sql Server. SQL Server in containers, Sql Server in the cloud, Sql Server on-premise, T-Sql fundamentals, advanced T-Sql, performance tuning, engine internals, HA/DR overview etc.</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">Beginner Data Science Day</title>
<url>https://wit.sqlugs.com/2021/06/11/data-platform-wit-beginner-data-science-day/</url>
<dateStart>20-August-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>20-August-2021</dateEnd>
<description>We are Data Platform WIT (women-in-tech) group and this is our next day long event featuring women speakers on beginner level data science topics. Our call for speakers is still open. We close CFS 8th August and meetup registration for attendance opens soon after.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Data Saturday #15 Plovdiv</title>
<url>https://datasaturdays.com/2021-08-28-datasaturday0015/</url>
<dateStart>28-Aug-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>28-Aug-2021</dateEnd>
<description>Data Saturday #15 Plovdiv is a free one-day event for professionals who use the Microsoft data platform. This community event offer content across data management, cloud. </description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Data Platform Virtual Summit 2021</title>
<url>https://dataplatformgeeks.com/dps2021/</url>
<dateStart>08-Sept-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>21-Sept-2021</dateEnd>
<description>DPS 2021 virtual conference will cover all the time zones. With 20+ Training Classes, 150+ Breakout Sessions and 100+ World’s Best Educators – DPS 2021 is a focused learning event on Microsoft Azure Data, Analytics - Artificial Intelligence. Attend LIVE and get the recordings (12 months streaming access).</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Data Saturday #11 Croatia</title>
<url>https://datasaturdays.com/2021-09-11-datasaturday0011/</url>
<dateStart>11-Sept-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>11-Sept-2021</dateEnd>
<description>Data Saturday #11 Croatia is a free one-day event for professionals who use the Microsoft data platform. This community event offer content across data management, cloud and hybrid architecture, analytics, business intelligence, AI, and more.</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">Data Platform Discovery Day</title>
<url>https://dataplatformdiscoveryday.com/</url>
<dateStart>21-September-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>21-September-2021</dateEnd>
<description>Focused on helping you take your first steps into the Microsoft Data Platform world and the next steps in your career journey…
Whether you’re an old hand wanting to learn something to expand your career, or someone who’s just heard about it and wants to learn more, everyone is welcome!
This time we’re also having expert panels between sessions discussing topics, and taking questions from the audience.</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community"><title lang="en">Future Data Driven Summit</title>
<url>http://datadrivencommunity.com</url>
<dateStart>29-Sept-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>29-Sept-2021</dateEnd>
<description>Future Data Driven is a marquee, online event focusing on the comprehensive Microsoft Data Platform. Our mission is to inform and update attendees with Data and AI, DevOps and DataOps, PowerBI and Visualization, Integration and Automation and cloud infrastructure. We are excited to welcome you to participate at our free first ever Future Data Driven online event.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Data Saturday #10 Sofia</title>
<url>https://datasaturdays.com/2021-09-11-datasaturday0011/</url>
<dateStart>09-Oct-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>09-Oct-2021</dateEnd>
<description>Data Saturday #10 Sofia is a free one-day event for professionals who use the Microsoft data platform. This community event offer content across data management, cloud and hybrid architecture, analytics, business intelligence, AI, and more. We are planning event to be a hybrid event.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">DBCC International 2021</title>
<url>https://sessionize.com/dbcc-international-2021/</url>
<dateStart>15-October-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>15-October-2021</dateEnd>
<description>After the success of the Data Blaster Community Conference (DBCC) in June and both DBCC events in 2020, we will be organizing DBCC International this year again.
On Friday October 15th, 2021 the time has come to continue the virtual conference format on an international level. In three parallel tracks, 21 short lectures are planned for you, which represent many topics from the Data Platform in a varied format and provide exciting content for both beginners and advanced participants.
The Teams links that you need to participate in the conference will be inserted on this page as soon as the schedule has been set. By the way, you don’t have to register, anyone who clicks on the corresponding team link can simply participate.</description>
</event>
 <event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Data Saturday #13 Minnesota</title>
<url>https://datasaturdays.com/2021-10-16-datasaturday0013/</url>
<dateStart>16-Oct-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>16-Oct-2021</dateEnd>
<description>A free virtual event for all data learners and professionals seeking to learn! This community event offer content across data management, cloud and hybrid architecture, analytics, business intelligence, AI, and more.  It will be held virtually due to pandemic.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">New Stars of Data</title>
<url>https://www.newstarsofdata.com</url>
<dateStart>22-October-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>22-October-2021</dateEnd>
<description>New Stars of Data is the event for new speakers in the Microsoft Data Platform space.
This online event is the perfect start for people who have not spoken at any large events before. We are searching for the next generation of speakers who want to take their first steps into the realm of presenting their ideas to an audience. 
We offer a mentoring program to each chosen speaker. A mentor is a seasoned speaker who will help craft and practice your session. They will also be on hand during the presentation as a host/mentor and be able to offer the support you need to deliver a fantastic presentation. </description>
</event>
<event category="Community"><title lang="en">GroupBy Conference</title>
<url>https://groupby.org/</url>
<dateStart>26-October-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>27-October-2021</dateEnd>
<description>GroupBy is data platform training by the community, for the community.
Each session will be 60-minutes in length, followed by 15-minutes for Q and A and 15-minutes for whimsy and fun. 
After submitting your session, the community votes on their top picks to present October 26-27!

On Tuesday, October 26 GroupBy Americas will present sessions at timeslots accessible for American timezones.
On Wednesday, October 27 GroupBy Europe will present sessions at timeslots accessible for European timezones.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">SQL Saturday Orlando 2021</title>
<url>https://sqlsaturday.com/2021-10-31-sqlsaturday1021/</url>
<dateStart>30-October-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>30-October-2021</dateEnd>
<description>SQL Saturday Orlando is a free one day training event for data platform professionals taking place on 30 Oct, 2021 in Orlando, FL.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Difinity</title>
<url>https://difinity.co.nz/</url>
<dateStart>01-Nov-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>02-Nov-2021</dateEnd>
<description>Difinity is the largest Microsoft Data, AI, Power BI, Power Platform and Business Applications Conference in New Zealand focusing on Data Platform, AI, Business Intelligence, Business Applications, Power Platform, and Analytics.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">PASS Summit 2021</title>
<url>https://passdatacommunitysummit.com/</url>
<dateStart>08-Nov-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>12-Nov-2021</dateEnd>
<description>Join us for this free online Summit and connect, share, and learn with 1000s of your peers from the global data platform community.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">SQL Server Live!</title>
<url>https://live360events.com/home.aspx</url>
<dateStart>15-Nov-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>19-Nov-2021</dateEnd>
<description>SQL Server Live!: Providing content for data professionals to do more with their Microsoft data platform investment. Sessions will cover performance tuning, security, reporting, data integration, and modernizing the SQL Server infrastructure.</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">Dev Intersection - Las Vegas</title>
<url>https://www.devintersection.com/#!/?track=sql</url>
<dateStart>7-Dec-2021</dateStart>
<dateEnd>9-Dec-2021</dateEnd>
<description>THE INTERSECTION OF CO-LOCATED TECHNOLOGY EVENTS: Microsoft SQL Server Azure SQL Conference and Azure + AI Conference</description>
</event>
<event category="Community">
<title lang="en">DataGrillen 2022</title>
<url>http://www.DataGrillen.com</url>
<dateStart>02-June-2022</dateStart>
<dateEnd>03-June-2022</dateEnd>
<description>Databases, Bratwurst, Bier
The most flavoursome Data Platform event on the planet</description>
</event>
</events>
